Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  - Subseries B: Private homes., 1939-1970.; 73 map folders
    - (1 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 152)
      - Soutter residence., 1953.; 6.; 5 items.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Robert Soutter.
    - (2 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 153)
      - McDowell "New England Farm House"., 1953.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 53-11. McDowell "New England Farm House"
        Oakdell Ln. Studio City, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and perspective.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Allyn McDowell.
      - Hexberg residence., 1953.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-20. Hexberg residence
        749 Linda Vista Ave. Pasadena, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E. M. Hexberg.
      - Marks residence., 1953.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 53-21. Marks residence
        6828 Simpson Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Tony Marks.
      - Lipp "Glen View" residence., 1953.; 4.; 15 items.
        Job Number 53-22. Lipp "Glen View" residence
        1680 Larco Way, Glendale, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Elmer Lipp.
      - Fielding residence., 1953.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-25. Fielding residence
        10768 Wheatland Ave. Shadow Hills, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Margie and Burt Fielding.
    - (3 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 154)
      - Rupe residence., 1953-54.; 1.; 14 items.
        Job Number 53-26. Rupe residence
        12469 Mulholland Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections, details and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Arthur N. Rupe.
      - Smalley residence., 1953.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-33. Smalley residence
        Wilbur Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F.J. Smalley Jr.
      - Prophet residence., 1953.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 53-36. Prophet residence
        Gable Dr. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. A. Prophet.
      - Salvail residence?, 1953.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-41. Salvail residence?
        Mulholland Drive?
        Original preliminary drawings: plans, elevations and section.
      - Moises residence., 1953.; 5.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-43. Moises residence
        Devonshire, Granada Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J.B. Moises.
      - O'meara residence., 1953.; 6.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-45. O'meara residence
        Cline Rd. Cold Canyon, Calabasas, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, section, elevations and perspective.
        Owner: Mrs. O'Meara.
    - (4 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 155)
      - Rosenthal residence., 1953-54.; 1.; 21 items.
        Job Number 53-47, 53-65, 54-38. Rosenthal residence
        1434 Jonesboro Dr. Original drawings: plan, sections, elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. Max Rosenthal.
      - Hollivet residence., 1953.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 53-48. Hollivet residence
        4926 Gloria Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, and elevations.
        Owner: Mrs. Albert E. Hollivet.
      - Von Walden residence., 1953.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 53-51. Von Walden residence
        2031 Roscomare Rd. Bel Air Highlands, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Sherman von Walden.
      - George residence., 1953-54.; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 53-52. George residence
        2366 Astral Dr. Los Angeles, CA. Original drawings: plans, sections and elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E. W. George.
      - Boskovich residence., 1953.; 5.; 6 items.
        Job Number 53-55. Boskovich residence
        Original drawings: plans, sections, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Philip Boskovich.
      - Roman dwelling., 1953.; 6.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-58. Roman dwelling
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Percy Roman.
    - (5 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 156)
      - Lea residence., 1953.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-59. Lea residence
        Terrace Drive St. Delano, CA. (Kern County).
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Lea.
      - Pacal duplex., 1953.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 53-60. Pacal duplex
        Clybourn Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Joseph Pacal.
      - Kauffman residence., 1953-1954.; 3.; 19 items.
        Job Number 53-62. Kauffman residence
        1486 Amalfi Dr. Pacific Palisades, CA.
        Legal correspondence and perspectives.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. M. Kauffman.
      - Russ Madsen residence., 1953.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-63. Russ Madsen residence
        Royal Woods Dr. Royal Woods, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Russ Madsen.
    - (1 of 4)., 1954 (Folder 157)
      - Max Rosenthal residences., 1954.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 54-4, 54-5. Max Rosenthal residences
        1370, 1380 Longworth Dr. Brentwood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, perspectives, interior and exterior elevations.
      - Ward residence., 1954.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 54-7. Ward residence
        4001 Royal Oak Place, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Preston Ward.
      - Hook residence., 1954.; 3.; 11 items.
        Job Number 54-18. Hook residence
        1261 Shadow Hill Way, Beverly Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. S. Hook Jr.
    - (2 of 4)., 1954 (Folder 158)
      - West residence., 1954.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 54-19. West residence
        Bakersfield, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Geo. West.
      - Russell residence., 1954.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 54-23. Russell residence
        Banio Court, Encino Knolls, Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.T. Russel.
      - Elder residence., 1954.; 3.; 13 items.
        Job Number 54-28. Elder residence
        16461 Garvin Dr. Sky Line Terrace, Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections, details and perspectives.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Neal Elder.
    - (3 of 4)., 1954 (Folder 159)
      - Whittaker dwelling., 1954.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 54-30. Whittaker dwelling
        4701 Encino Ave.
        Owner: Mrs. Whittaker.
      - Sidell residence., 1954.; 2.; 12 items.
        Job Number 54-40. Sidell residence
        5266 Amestoy Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Chester Sidell.
      - McGregor residence., 1954.; 3.; 14 items.
        Job Number 54-41. McGregor residence
        16096 Royal Oak Rd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Arch McGregor.
    - (4 of 4)., 1954 (Folder 160)
      - Price dwelling., 1954.; 1.; 12 items.
        Job Number 54-45. Price dwelling
        429 N. Garfield St. Hinsdale, Illinois.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, details and perspectives.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W.F. Price.
      - Lee residence., 1954.; 2.; 13 items.
        Job Number 54-47. Lee residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Pinky Lee.
      - Miller residence., 1954.; 3.; 10 items.
        Job Number 54-51. Miller residence
        19202 Santa Rita St. Orangeland Estates, Tarzana.
        Structural calculations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jonas Miller.
      - Morris residence., 1954.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 54-54. Morris residence
        Original drawings: plans and interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mrs. Maud Morris.
      - Nelson residence., 1954.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 54-55. Nelson residence
        5641 Wineland Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing and copy of site.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. N. E. Nelson.
    - (1 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 161)
      - Hunter residence., 1955.; 1.; 1 item.
        Hunter residence
        Owner: Mr. Hunter.
      - Morrison residence., 1955.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 55-3. Morrison residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W.A. Morrison.
      - Lefevre residence., 1955.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 55-4. Lefevre residence
        5080 San Feliciano Dr. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Gerald Lefevre.
      - Jones residence., 1955.; 4.; 8 items.
        Job Number 55-6. Jones residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George W. Jones.
      - Frenzel residence., 1955.; 5.; 6 items.
        Job Number 55-18. Frenzel residence
        Ridgeview Dr. Glendale, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Frenzel.
    - (2 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 162)
      - Somers residence., 1955.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 55-22. Somers residence
        9618 Arrowood Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
      - Hance residence., 1955.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 55-24. Hance residence
        Adlon Rd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J.W. Hance.
      - Deming residence (2 of 6)., 1955.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 55-25. Deming residence
        11677 Laurelwood Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Norman Deming.
      - McRee residence., 1955.; 4.; 6 items.
        Job Number 55-26. McRee residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. McRee.
    - (3 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 163)
      - Vaiana residence., 1955.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 55-27. Vaiana residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. James Vaiana.
      - Sharpe residence., 1955.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 55-33. Sharpe residence
        13745 Valerio, Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, elevation and sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Stanley Sharpe.
      - Reid residence., 1955-1957.; 3.; 10 items.
        Job Number 55-34. Reid residence
        5214 Coulter Rd. Hidden Hills, LA County, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Mrs. Elizabeth Reid.
      - Brown residence., 1955.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 55-35. Brown residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Joseph Brown.
      - Billingsley residence., 1955.; 5.; 16 items.
        Job Number 55-38. Billingsley residence
        23330 Cohasset, Canoga Park, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Glenn Billingsley.
    - (4 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 164)
      - Madsen-Fox residence., 1955.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 55-41. Madsen-Fox residence
        Royal Woods, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. V. R. Madsen & Mrs. Francis M. Fox.
      - Cahill residence., 1955.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 55-42. Cahill residence
        9541 Cherokee Lane, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Cahill.
      - Colton residence., 1955.; 3.; 16 items.
        Job Number 55-44. Colton residence
        4019 Valley Meadow Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. M.M. Colton.
      - Bergerman residence., 1955.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 55-54. Bergerman residence
        Stonewood Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Stanley Bergerman.
    - (5 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 165)
      - Bereny residence., 1955.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 55-56. Bereny residence
        11579 Meadowgate Rd. Royal Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. A.M. Bereny.
      - Boesche residence., 1955.; 2.; 22 items.
        Job Number 55-60. Boesche residence
        13552 Contour Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings and copies: plans, interior and exterior elevations, section and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F.M. Boesch.
    - (6 of 6)., 1955 (Folder 166)
      - Weaver residence., 1955.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 55-66. Weaver residence
        4907 Longridge Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G.T. Weaver.
      - Frankel residence., 1955.; 2.; 12 items.
        Job Number 55-67. Frankel residence
        19821 Henshaw St. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D.L. Frankel.
      - Patty residence., 1955.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 55-68. Patty residence
        4067 Cody Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H.M. Patty.
      - Johnson residence., 1955.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 55-75. Johnson residence
        16115 Liggett St. Sepulveda, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and sections
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Raymond O. Johnson.
    - (1 of 4)., 1956 (Folder 167)
      - Leiter mountain cabin., 1956.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 56-3. Leiter mountain cabin
        Palisades Dr. Arrowhead Woods, Arrowhead, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Leiter.
      - Stanley residence., 1956.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 56-9. Stanley residence
        1230 Shadow Hill Way, Beverly Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Lowell Stanley.
      - Subert residence & garage., 1956.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 56-10. Subert residence & garage
        4733 Libbet Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. J.H. Subert Jr.
    - (2 of 4)., 1956 (Folder 168)
      - Papaleo residence., 1956.; 1.; 9 items.
        Job Number 56-11. Papaleo residence
        17041 Magnolia Blvd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Anthony Papaleo.
      - Bernardi residence., 1956.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 56-13. Bernardi residence
        14518 Sherman Way, Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. E. Bernardi.
      - Finsterwald residence., 1956.; 3.; 5 items.
        Job Number 56-13. Finsterwald residence
        Excelente Dr. Woodland Hills, CA.
      - McGaffy residence., 1956.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 56-27 (988). McGaffy residence
        Tarzana Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D. R. McGaffy.
    - (3 of 4)., 1956 (Folder 169)
      - Bair residence., 1956-1957.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 56-29. Bair residence
        3850 Ostbye Rd. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Watt Bair.
      - Yarnell residence., 1956.; 2.; 16 items.
        Job Number 56-37. Yarnell residence
        Encino Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Ellis M. Yarnell.
    - (4 of 4)., 1956 (Folder 170)
      - Hartman residence., 1956.; 1.; 14 items.
        Job Number 56-44. Hartman residence
        5747 Jed Smith Rd. Hidden Hills, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. S.A. Hartman.
      - Blaser residence., 1956.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 56-54. Blaser residence
        754 Peach St. San Luis Obispo, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, interior and exterior elevations and section.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. G. Blaser.
      - Robinson residence & attached garage., 1956-1957.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 56-57. Robinson residence & attached garage
        3624 Shannon Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Leopold Robinson.
    - (1 of 4)., 1957 (Folder 171)
      - Pyke residence., 1957.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 57-3. Pyke residence
        11227 Encino Ave. Granada Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dorie Pyke.
      - Sanett residence., 1957.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 57-4. Sanett residence
        1943 San Ysidro Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Ben Sanett.
      - Becker residence., 1957.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 57-5. Becker residence
        Valley Meadow Rd. Royal Oaks, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dale L. Becker.
    - (2 of 4)., 1957 (Folder 172)
      - Hart residence., 1957.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 57-11. Hart residence
        La Carlota Rd. Covina, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Richard Hart.
      - Phillips residence., 1957.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 57-21. Phillips residence
        4747 Corbin Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Descriptions of materials document.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Leonard Phillips.
      - Gaines residence., 1957-1958.; 3.; 12 items.
        Job Number 57-31. Gaines residence
        16237 Quemada Rd. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Gaines.
      - Apter residence., 1957.; 4.; 8 items.
        Job Number 57-34. Apter residence
        19329 Palomar Place. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Apter.
    - (3 of 4)., 1957 (Folder 173)
      - Francais residence., 1957.; 23 items.
        Job Number 57-38. Francais residence
        4487 Woodley Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Richard Francais.
    - (4 of 4)., 1957 (Folder 174)
      - Waterman residence & 2 car garage., 1957.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 57-44. Waterman residence & 2 car garage
        2256 Santa Anna Ave. Costa Mesa, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Waterman.
      - Stadin residence., 1957.; 2.; 10 items.
        Job Number 57-47. Stadin residence
        3380 Chevy Chase Dr. Glendale, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Ragnar Stadin.
      - Fox residence & carport., 1957.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 57-52. Fox residence & carport
        3270 Dunsmere Dr. Glendale, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Warren Fox.
    - (1 of 2)., 1958 (Folder 175)
      - Wilner residence., 1958.; 1.; 5 items.
        Wilner residence
        Empress Ave. Encino Estates, CA.
        Copy of drawings, source unknown, signed by H.J. Fiege For design & tract restrictions, approved by Encino Estates Architectural Board: plans, elevations, sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wilner.
      - Wright residence., 1958.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 58-1. Wright residence
        Broken Arrow Rd. Borrego Springs, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wright.
      - Hrock residence., 1958.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 58-6. Hrock residence
        440 Albertson St. Covina, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. William J. Hrock.
      - Crank residence., 1958.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 58-20. Crank residence
        2121 El Roble Ln. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs.Chet Crank.
    - (2 of 2)., 1958 (Folder 176)
      - Mullender residence., 1958.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 58-24. Mullender residence
        Santa Clara St.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J.D. Mullender.
      - Miller residence., 1958.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 58-27. Miller residence
        3546 Alginet Dr. Encino Estates, Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jos. Miller.
      - Vlasek residence., 1958.; 3.; 1 item.
        Vlasek residence
        2111 Sunnybank Dr. Le Canada, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, elevations and sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. Vlasek.
    - ., 1959 (Folder 177)
      - Barker residence., 1959.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 59-5. Barker residence
        7056 Macapa Dr. Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections and interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. M.L. Barker.
      - Peters residence., 1959.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 59-16. Peters residence
        1770 West Ridge Rd. West Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Alex Peters.
      - Fields residence., 1959.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 59-23. Fields residence
        2236 Beverly Glen, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Herbert Fields.
      - Wilson Cottage., 1959.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 59-24. Wilson Cottage
        17132 Rancho St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George C. Wilson.
    - ., 1960 (Folder 178)
      - Johnson residence., 1960.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 60-15. Johnson residence
        2510 Outpost Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Beverly Johnson.
      - Fox residence., 1960.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 60-17. Fox residence
        1763 Cielito Dr. Glendale, CA.
      - Caliva residence., 1960.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 60-18. Caliva residence
        Wrightwood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Cal Caliva.
      - Haas residence., 1960.; 4.; 7 items.
        Job Number 60-36. Haas residence
        33950 Pacific Coast Highway, Malibu, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dossie B. Haas.
    - (1 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 179)
      - Van Beveren residence., 1961.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 61-1.
        4214 Farmdale, North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. C. L. Van Beveren.
      - Brown residence., 1961.; 2.; 14 items.
        Job Number 61-14.
        9842 Lloydcrest Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Ted Brown.
      - Salvail residence., 1961.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 61-30.
        Owner: Merle Salvail.
    - (2 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 180)
      - Clark residence., 1961.; 1.; 21 items.
        Job Number 61-35.
        Fairway Rd. La Jolla, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. Clark.
      - Bartosh residence., 1961.; 2.; 12 items.
        Job Number 61-39.
        Schuyler Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.A. Bartosh.
      - Eiklor residence., 1961.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 61-40.
        5674 Holly Oak, Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W.K. Eiklor.
    - ., 1962-1963 (Folder 181)
      - Richardson residence., 1962.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 62-9. Richardson residence
        3810 Randolph Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. M. Richardson.
      - Newberry residence., 1963.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 63-5. Newberry residence
        13313 Chandler Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Louis Newberry.
      - Savage residence., 1963.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 63-6. Savage residence
        42040 Tongareva St. Malibu West, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E.S. Savage.
      - Spurck residence., 1963.; 3.; 13 items.
        Job Number 63-22. Spurck residence
        22615 Erwin St. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Vada Spurck.
    - ., 1964-1970 (Folder 182)
      - Marinelli residence., 1964.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 64-2. Marinelli residence
        41995 Tongareva St. Malibu West, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. A. C. Marinelli.
      - Diekmann residence., 1964.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 64-10. Diekmann residence
        340 Vista Place, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Klem Diekmann.
      - Williams residence, store and office building., 1966.; 3.; 3 items.
        Williams residence, store and office building
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and perspective.
        Owner: Guy Williams.
      - Harris residence., 1966.; 4.; 8 items.
        Job Number 66-7. Harris residence
        16014 Skytop Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Melvin I. Harris.
      - Green residence., 1966.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 66-23. Green residence
        13525 Delano St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Green.
      - Trebaol residence., 1970.; 6.; 2 items.
        Job Number 70-20. Trebaol residence
        Owner: Fr. Herve Trebaol.
  - Subseries C: Additions and renovations., 1939-1968.; 30 map folders
    Alterations to existing residential structures. Descriptions include references to projects in Subseries B., where appropriate.
    - Miscellaneous. (Folder 183)
      - Terrell residence., no date.; 1.; 1 item.
        Addition to Terrell residence
        Owner: Maurice Terrell.
      - Zandler residence., no date.; 2.; 1 item.
        Addition to Zandler residence
        4434 Wortser Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E.J. Zandler.
      - Jensen garage building., no date.; 3.; 1 item.
        Jensen garage building
        6821 Hinds Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, section, elevations and detail.
      - Furnish guest house., no date.; 4.; 1 item.
        Furnish guest house
        13908 Bessemer St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Furnish.
      - Lytton car port., no date.; 5.; 1 item.
        Lytton car port
        Original drawing: plan, elevation and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Bart Lytton.
      - Defore residence., no date.; 6.; 1 item.
        Additions and remodeling of Defore residence
        Original drawing: plans and elevation.
      - Snow residence., no date.; 7.; 2 items.
        Alterations and additions to Snow residence
        6603 Mammoth, Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Hazel F. Snow.
    - ., 1939-1945 (Folder 184)
      - Saddle Rock Ranch., 1939.; 1.; 5 items.
        Saddle Rock Ranch- garages & servants quarters
        Saddle Rock Ranch, Big Sur, CA.
        Copy of drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations.
        Original document: Specifications for construction
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Lathrop Brown.
      - Whitbeck Barn., 1945.; 2.; 3 items.
        Whitbeck Barn
        16426 Chatsworth St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: plans. Sections, elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Frank Whitbeck.